Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers GEN MSS 868
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; 7; 154203; 15.62 Linear Feet (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings, 154243
    - 7" vinyl sound discs, 154305
      - Jandl, Ernst. Laut und Luise, 1968; 154322 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Jandl, Ernst. hosi + anna, 1971; 154321 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Jandl, Ernst. Der künstliche Baum, undated; 154320 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Mac Low, Jackson. 1st Milarepa Gatha, 1976; 154319 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Macromassa. Darlia Microtonica, 1978; 154318 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Mallander, J.O. Decompositions, 1970; 154317 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Moineau, Jean-Claude. Manuel de conversation, undated; 154316 (Box 61 (Record Album Storage))
      - Nannucci, Maurizio. Parole 1976, 1979; 154315 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Nannucci, Maurizio. Parole/mots/words/wörter, 1979; 154314 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Numminen, M.A. The World is / In order to, undated; 154313 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Pernes, Thomas. Zur Eröffnung, 1986; 154312 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Reuterswärd, Carl Frederik. Hållertal & Tandförtunga, undated; 154311 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Schalss, Gerda. vogelsang / sonneborn, 1991; 154310 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Shrewsbury Pumping Station. The Music of Machiner: Volume One, 1968; 154309 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Stern, Anatol. Kraj. Wieś i miasto, undated; 154308 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Stock, Hausen und Walkman. Ventilating deer, 1997; 154307 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
      - Stock, Hausen und Walkman. Buy me / Sue me, 1997; 154306 (Box 62 (Record Album Storage))
    - Audiocassettes, commercially released and non-commercial, 154271
      Boxes 63-71 and 80 (sound recordings): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&99f63fce-851e-4e9a-b0ab-4b90fafce653
      - Baobab. "L'in / Canto del verso" (1 of 4), 1994 June; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:31:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 47, Item barcode 39002109975657)
        Includes I. Poesia Dello Spazio, II. La Voce in Sintesi, III. Sul Confine In/Verso (I Parte)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&561ce077-5227-46ac-8534-8ad61bd0b292
      - Baobab. "L'in / Canto del verso" (2 of 4), 1994 June; 154303; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:18:44 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 47, Item barcode 39002093778539)
        Includes III. Sul Confine In/Verso (II Parte), IV. La Parola Cantata, V. Sull'in/Verso Confine
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&676e2f4a-e1d6-4b9a-86d9-b1157628f16f
      - Baobab. "L'in / Canto del verso" (3 of 4), 1994 June; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:21:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Low level recording on the right channel from 1:02:55-1:07:09. (Box 47, Item barcode 39002109975665)
        Includes VI. In Media Stat Versus, VII. Versi in Jazz, VIII. Note D'Ironia, IX. La Voce al Cubo (I Parte)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&63275a3e-652d-45e6-9989-501c4a2a528c
      - Baobab. "L'in / Canto del verso" (4 of 4), 1994 June; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:30:30 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. The audio is recorded at a low level on the right channel from 5:14-14:00. (Box 47, Item barcode 39002109975673)
        Includes IX. La Voce Al Cubo (II Parte), X. Montaggi Di/Versi, Documenti
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&fd5849fd-1dfd-4fff-99da-bd66e52e92bb
      - Ars Nova. "Far out at Sea" (CAS 19), 1984 March 10; 154304; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:54:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502886)
        Far Out at Sea by Morrow, Borum, Andersen. Performance on Danmarks Radio by ARS Nova, directed by Bo Holten, spoken voice of mermaid Emily Fader, sung voice of mermaid Agnete Christiansen. Duration 1 hour, live from Nikolay Church, Copenhagen.
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&444e8792-b7dc-432f-8ea8-173bf0e014da
      - Chopin, Henri. "A -> K" (CAS 17), undated; 154302; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:37:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of hum can be heard. The program was recorded at a very high level. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502894)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&ce22d8e9-d82d-4dc8-8c42-079ed5914427
      - Chopin, Henri." K -> T" (CAS 3), undated; 154301; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:35:39 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of buzz can be heard on the tape. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502902)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&89de986c-9750-4918-b804-16c79d0d7114
      - Chopin, Henri. "1983", 154300; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:50:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502910)
        Contents of the cassette are listed.
        Face 1/Face 2
        1. Symphonie en Rut Jambette, 1982: 5' 35"
        2. Trio d'Eté, (1), 1979: 12' 12"
        3. Voyage in California, (2), 1983: 9' 15"
        1. Sol air, 1961-1964: 9' 46"
        2. 2500, ou les Grenouilles d'Aristophane, ou la Fortune, (3), 1967: 4' 57"
        3. Nous n'avons pas voix au Chapitre, 1983: 3' 35"
        4. Jouissance des lèvres, 1983: 4' 37"
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bdf717bd-1aa8-4a6b-b7ed-dc20ada16a40
      - Chopin, Henri. "Audiopoems 1956-1980", undated; 154299; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:51:13 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502928)
        Contents of the audiocassette are listed below.
        Side 1/Side 2
        "Rouge", audiopoem 1956. 3' 04".
        "Dynamisme intégral", audiopoem 1973. 4' 07".
        "French lesson", audiopoem 1974. Unpublished. 5' 15".
        "Hoppa Back", 1970. 5' 55".
        "Pêche de Nuit", 1957. 11' 40".
        "Tête-tête", 1971-73. Unpublished. 3' 40".
        "L'Agrippe des Droits", 1980. 10' 06".
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&dd22bb50-a7c9-4fef-ba3c-93865179cc71
      - Chopin, Henri. "Audiopoems 1956-1980", undated; 154298; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:51:21 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); This appears to be a duplicate. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502936)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&41017117-ba7d-4c53-aec0-f3d3f1118859
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le Corpsbis" (CAS 2), undated; 154297; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:52:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502944)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&16cc9d7d-8746-4199-b25c-fe883fe006c9
      - Chopin, Henri. "Le Voyage Labiovélaire" (CAS 4), undated; 154296; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:23:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502951)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b4697957-2920-4046-92ca-5fba0e4e5f7b
      - Chopin, Henri. "Pirouttes" (CAS 1A), undated; 154295; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:09:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); There are recorded silences from 5:30-14:19 and 43:19-44:08. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502969)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&331ae57b-235b-4f70-bd8d-67e0fd0e3ae2
      - Chopin, Henri. "Pirouttes" (CAS 1B), undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:05:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502977)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&1ead28be-a7c6-42b9-bfcc-8874aa50c887
      - Chopin, Henri. "Poesie Sonore" (CAS 5), undated; 154294; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:08:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static and a high amount of buzz can be heard on the tape. Clicks and pops can also be heard. The program is distorted at times. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502985)
        Emissions 9 et 10
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&c331279d-f31a-4922-81fc-cdf0dbd36b2d
      - Dana, Llys. "Songs 1,2" (CAS 18), undated; 154293; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:22:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104502993)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&de1b751a-f606-4d38-b6cb-26f3bb7f70c1
      - Duke, Walwicz, and Zurbrugg. "Sound Poetry" (CAS 21), 1987 February; 154292; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:30:55 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104503009)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&5fd8da54-2ed7-44c5-8228-5756ad9e340b
      - Machine for Making Sense. "On Second Thoughts" (CAS 6), 1993; 154291; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:50:05 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104503017)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b8e0848a-1b6d-470f-9cb5-73ad435f7cee
      - Pi.O. "Pi.O. Sound Poetry" (CAS 7), undated; 154290; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:18:40 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Buzz can be heard on the tape. (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104503025)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&016bcff3-3757-406a-ac9b-e988264dbcd6
      - Pissier, Ph. "Mi-Ange, Mi-Demon" (CAS 8), undated; 154289; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:42:49 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 63, Item barcode 39002104503033)
        Philippe Pissier (85-86); en et mis en voix par Jéan-pierre Espil (87)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6187f2e2-7f27-4bbf-aeac-d8eae0a45af3
      - Radio Bourges. "Les Poemes" (CAS 16), undated; 154288; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:49:34 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard. Audio in the left channel was recorded at a lower volume on the tape. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503165)
        Apollinaile G O 11; Seuphor; Pansaers; Neuhuys; PAB; H.C. Arp.; Theo van Does.; Picalia
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&46c71d7c-985c-4b55-ad54-44d0300a8957
      - Sarenco. "Sarenco Anthology" (CAS 9), 1978-1979; 154287; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:32:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. Audio is silent on the left channel from 1:22:23-1:29:41. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503173)
        "Accumulaliou"/L'Azmaniana" (Homage to Armian), 1979
        "C'est [Vzai] De Vree", 1979
        "Yo ablo", 1978
        "Barb (a) ra", 1978
        "Sono un poeta", 1978
        "Concerto in 1a minore", 1978
        "Piéa Fausse", 1979
        "Cosu resta", 1978
        "Peom 12. 78", 1978
        "Music 78"
        "Trinidad", 1979
        "La balalaika", 1979
        "Desiderio", 1979
        "Die Zauberflöte", 1978
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6b036dc2-b33b-44a4-8588-09e2ac63ae58
      - "New Sounds Gallery" (CAS 10), 1984 October 30 & 31; 154286; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:45:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503181)
        CFRO-FM; Vancouver
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6f03c0a8-b05c-4f16-99c3-34d3ed0410c0
      - "Poesie pour Rire, Poesie Sonore" (CAS 11), 1991 April-May; 154285; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:14:10 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503199)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&5bde0cee-aeee-49e1-80fa-30a2d36dff82
      - RP "Chopin" (CAS 12) 1 of 2, 1982 September 3; 154284; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:03:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503207)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&acff6d41-6817-4a3c-8d2a-0c1038620020
      - RP "Chopin" (CAS 13) 2 of 2, 1982 September 3; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:25:18 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503215)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&07f43590-468b-4bea-a701-c13adfc952f0
      - A. C. R. De A a Z de H. Chopin et P. Zumthor (CAS 14) 1 of 2, 1992 May 31; 154283; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:37:09 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503223)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&21c5ac49-3113-46d8-8ffb-0df0bdb51b97
      - A. C. R. De A a Z de H. Chopin et P. Zumthor (CAS 15) 2 of 2, 1992 May 31; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:22:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503231)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&0facc94b-5bef-4abe-9172-645a10c95d2b
      - Subtile Voice by C. W. de H. C. (CAS 20), 1985 April; 154282; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:10:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503249)
        San Jose, CA
        1) Subtile Voice, 6'17"
        2) Round Destruction for a poem, 4'
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&10c8f218-d093-4a5a-a533-c24b79dfdb23
      - Unidentified, undated; 154281; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:00:29 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503256)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&d1c6e724-6089-4007-b2e8-3db750f896fb
      - Unidentified, undated; 154280; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:17:23 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 64, Item barcode 39002104503264)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8554a2cb-aab0-4f2b-9a85-bca6de673326
      - Works by Chopin, unsorted, 154279; (15 audiocassettes)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&3d970153-acf1-4d38-a1d8-aee94487a146
        - Pira, Marc. 3 études de mécanique sonore naturelle, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:34:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 65, Item barcode 39002109889973)
          Face A: Petite cuisine concrète; Face B: Vent faible à modéré * Aquaphonie nº 1
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&46e1b3c9-5691-477c-b39a-64115559d1ac
        - Bernstein, Buck, la Palma, Piombino, Wendt and Zweig. Lobby Newsletter 18/19, 1982-1983; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:58:04 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002109889981)
          There is a list of contents included with the audiocassette.
          Side 1: Paul Buck
          Seduction in Cars (4.10)
          The Bleed Stocking in Thigh (4.50)
          (extracts from) Journies to the Perpendicular (8.15)
          Nick Piombino - Phase (3.00)
          Untitled (2.54)
          Untitled (1.52)
          Untitled (1.31)
          As in Me (2.11)
          Side 2:
          Charles Bernstein - Islets/Irritations Azoot D'Puund (6.43 and 3.44)
          Marina la Palma - Ixiva Portal Exo (3.48)
          Ellen Zweig - Green Silk (6.48)
          Larry Wedt - What is Man? (8.10)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&6bcab174-7a22-41ad-aee4-d83ed6ad3440
        - Media - Space, 1982 March 14; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:28:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002109889999)
          A list of contents include:
          poor australia
          grand america
          be right
          confrontation
          i don't wanu
          disappearing
          perth
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b534747e-cafa-48d7-bba2-d87d3dae3b56
        - Schwerner, Armand and Velez, Glen. New Wilderness Summer Solstice, 1984-06-19; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:28:42 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 65, Item barcode 39002109890005)
          at 8BC
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2c349458-ea50-46a2-a301-22a55c4627c2
        - Vonna-Michell, e.e. and Fisher, Allen. Chest Breath & Car Wash Interview, 1978 summer; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:19:52 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502589)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&2f32ca9e-7de3-4e70-ad1d-52d7571ff8b6
        - Eclatement & Limitation - Taliesin, 1980; 1 Audiocassettes (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502597)
          Songs listed on the audiocassette are as follows:
          intrigues
          solitude
          les dames de la cour au palais du roy
          l'homme noble
          jour et nuit
          loyauté
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e98746e1-7806-4327-8fd2-430a4ea993f8
        - Heinrich, Michael. Lyrics, 1992 December; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:15:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502605)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&605ac719-ac1f-4e6d-843a-3a2d0c358f17
        - Sauvagnac, Nicole. (Théatre de l'Immédiat), 1982; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:37:11 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); High frequency background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502621)
          Sculpter la parole du vent. 1/Discussion aquatique; 2/Etude sur le vent.
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&33d06b12-4e90-400d-bf56-03b3e549043f
        - Sauvagnac, Nicole. (Théátre de I'Immédiat), 1982; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:36:36 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502639)
          Sculpter la parole du vent. 1. Discussion aquatique, 2. Etude sur le vent; Dolby B, stereo
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&09513947-0011-47bc-b330-d9777fce244f
        - Vizents, A., Khakrabarty, Amanda. Media-Space Genetics, 1983 June; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:21:24 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502647)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&f9c178e7-72e0-419c-9a9e-4711f687ab9e
        - Le sonosaure/Le livre sonore, 1967; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:27:12 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502654)
          The contents of the audiocassette are listed as follows:
          Kinkao (14'22")
          Petites orgues (7'28")
          Tribal (7'28")
          Machine (10')
          Maounishnou (5')
          Queiques formules utiles (6'34")
          Au-delà des machines (7'14")
          S'abolir sonore (14'30")
          Eha! (7'12")
          La mort d'Antonin Artaud (8')
          Rire construit (4'50")
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&b828fb63-ea91-428f-a7fa-eca66419cb11
        - Heinrich, Michael. Lyrics, 1992 December; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:15:50 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502662)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&51f566d8-dbde-4b90-83cc-fdaedba1ab10
        - Espace Effondrement Les Yeux Fermés, 1986?; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:29:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502670)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&5da74fd0-1d38-45de-8d58-771265cc4f1d
        - Das Synthetische Mischgewebe. La Boîte de Doolittle part I, II, III, 1989 February; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:49:57 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502860)
          Voices and sounds of animals, recorded by various institutions around the world. Produced in a 8-track studio with snakes, pigs, orcas, fishes, insects, bats, penguins, birds, shacals, leopards...
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&32ef945a-7bb3-45ed-a505-9d105d935666
        - Mac Low, Jackson. New Wilderness Audiographics, 1977; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:57:33 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. A high amount of buzz can be heard. (Box 65, Item barcode 39002104502878)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&e20cd739-e774-4390-85dd-8521e5657d1d
      - Works by Chopin, unsorted, 154278; (35 audiocassettes)
        https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&099b4c80-55b5-4fed-9619-aaa0c43b40c3
        - Kostelanetz, Richard. Audio Art, 1980; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:46:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Audio is muffled at times. There is a high amount of hiss on the tape. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503629)
          Stereo. This audiocassette includes: "This is My Poem", "Plateaux", "Alphabet", "Praying to the Lord", "Foreshortenings", "Counting", "Declaration of Independence", "Excelsior", "Richard Kostelanetz, plus commentary.
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&7a55239f-5bf2-4158-9455-7ec5a55ba5c2
        - Kucharz. Canal St. (City Street Scenes I), undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:16:22 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of hiss and background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503637)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&8d364df0-c8e3-4bc2-b915-0eb97ac091b0
        - Thomas, Martin. Home Front Manhattan: An Acoustic Essay on Homelessness and the Gulf War, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:58:53 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503645)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&58d6497a-b222-47f7-bf37-89fcd11e1217
        - Pont, Gèrard. "A François Dupiêre", 1983 March; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:06:01 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503652)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&63037fb4-ca57-4dc3-ad60-1bc5015a8903
        - Untitled, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; This cassette is blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503660)
        - Buck, Paul and Parant, Jean-Luc. Reading xxxx7/Tik, undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:08:06 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503678)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&edc8f53b-6d82-4351-81fc-466afc90fa4f
        - Miccini, Eugenio. Il Soma, Le Soma, El Soma, 1978-1991; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:23:14 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503686)
          Other contents listed on the audiocassette include: Della Probità Dell' Informal/One (1991) and Alfabeto (1978)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&9c92c4c9-54e5-4d2b-a117-d631d6d1c3ef
        - Diede[?], Yau[?], Shrei/Aux Levres Du Nid, Le Silence, 1973 and 1984; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:42:19 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The audio is silent from 9:38-10:17. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503694)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&a494d2d0-9496-49ac-a4fe-24abf0766446
        - Loiseau, Pierre. Poévie, 1993 March 11; 1 Audiocassettes; 01:31:46 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503702)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&bd714cab-e6c4-492a-941d-5feb31e8c814
        - Rebotier, Jacques. "Poésie sur Parole", undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:43:47 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503710)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&dd3b64cb-6b1f-4393-afb2-f6f1c774b039
        - Rebotier, Jacques. "Poésie sur Parole", undated; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:28:00 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503728)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&534163a0-0dbd-44d7-a61c-49a221fb678b
        - Amirkhanian, Charles. New Works 1981-1982, 1983 May 30; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:43:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm) (Box 66, Item barcode 39002104503736)